Brandee Cheung

brandeedcheung@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/brandeecheung/ • BrandeeCheungPortfolio.com 520-401-6182

Qualifications Summary

Proactive and creative Software Engineer, Web Developer, Graphic Designer and Social Media Manager adept at identifying customer needs through extensive analysis and research to consistently deliver top-notch content designed to promote brands and increase profits. Experienced in collaborating with diverse teams on projects, operations, and branding initiatives.

Experience

Owner and Operator | BXDXC LLC. Media

December 2019 – Present

- Managed social media platforms (FB/IG/Google) for paid ads and promotions.
- Organized photo and video shoots, edited content using Adobe CC.
- Developed and designed effective websites, including e-commerce.

Director of Graphic Design | Social Media Manager | DYPER, Phoenix, AZ 2018 – 2019

- Orchestrated photo shoots and created social media content.
- Increased sales through promotions and creative collateral.
- Managed large-scale ad budgets on social media platforms.

Graphic Designer | Data Analyst | Uber, Phoenix, AZ

2017 - 2018

- Designed visuals and graphics; collected and analyzed national data.
- Created presentations and optimized Google spreadsheets.

Social Media/Design Consultant | Dreylon Vang Sequence1 Media, Mesa, AZ 2016 – 2017

- Planned, designed, and implemented website and social media content.
- Contributed to shoot settings and edited using Adobe Photoshop and After Effects.

Manager | Events Marketing | Maya Day and Nightclub, Scottsdale, AZ

2014 - 2017

- Coordinated staffing and events; trained staff to improve customer service.
- Managed social media platforms and created event-related content.

Social Media Output | Graphic Designer | Ocotillo, Chandler, AZ 2013 – 2014

Produced and posted graphics for promotions and daily updates.

Graphic Designer & Social Media Intern | Soul Carrier

2013 - 2015

Education

Bachelor of Science in Graphic Information Technology & Web Development

Graduated Cum Laude, 2017

Arizona State University - Ira A. Fulton School of Engineering, Tempe, AZ

Professional Training

Advanced Social Media Strategy Training – Influential Summit Attendee, 2018

Technical Proficiencies

- Full Stack Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Python
- Adobe Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Lightroom
- Other Tools: CAD, autoCAD, RHYNO, Sketchup, Microsoft Office, Google Suite

Key Skills

Lifecycle Project Management | Graphic Design | Social Media Management | Brand Development | Ads & Promos | Content Production | Web Design & Development | Photography & Editing | Staff Training & Leadership | Customer Service | Data Analysis | Market Trend Research